VICTORVOSKOVSKY@GMAIL.COM

VIC-VOSKOVSKY.GITHUB.IO/ * @COALESCENCEGG

1+(224) 595-5517

EDUCATION

DATA SCIENCE IMMERSIVE

GENERAL ASSEMBLY, CHICAGO | GRADUATED - 2020

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN FINANCE

DEPAUL UNIVERSITY, CHICAGO | GRADUATED - 2014

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

GENERAL ASSEMBLY - DATA SCIENCE FELLOW

CHICAGO, IL | MARCH 2020 - JUNE 2020

- Completed 12-week, 450+ hour immersive Data Science course in June, advancing my knowledge of Data Science.
- Coded several supervised and unsupervised predictive models using languages like Python, SQL and Scala.
- Completed 5 rigorous Data Science projects in a 12 week sprint, which culminated with a final capstone project.
- Harnessed computer science techniques to solve regression, classification, NLP & Neural Network problems.
- Created a ranking algorithm for Riot Games League of Legends to analyze and predict 2020 Worlds Tournament.
- Practiced skills to predict housing prices, perform hypothesis tests, systematically scrape the web, predict hurricane damage and interpret results to general audiences.

FINANCIAL ANALYST (BERKSHIRE HATHAWAY ACCOUNT)

INSURANCE AUTO AUCTIONS | OCT 2017 - NOV 2018

- Advised GEICO account director on complex business decisions with over 500k vehicles sold annually.
- Assisted leadership on large CAT reporting initiatives which analysed a database with 3m units sold per year.
- Assisted national account managers in making concise financial decisions based on current & historical data.
- Launched & administered reports on business metrics using Report Builder, Tableau & Excel primarily.
- Lead all Tableau implementations and deployment projects to phase out legacy systems.

BUSINESS OPERATIONS & STRATEGY ANALYST

KUNUNU, COM / MONSTER. COM, BOSTON, MA | JUL 2016 - AUG 2017

- Implemented, launched and administered DOMO & Tableau using AWS, Google Analytics and external data sources.
- Developed sales lead ranking algorithm to assist in national sales effort & participated in Salesforce integration.
- Headed big data migration projects between Kununu and Monster.com using SQL, Big Query, AWS and Excel.
- Worked directly with executives to create a robust sales funnel using Data.com, Salesforce and more.
- Reported & advised executives on company performance using agreed upon KPI's periodically.
- Point of contact for all data projects between Marketing, Sales and Finance departments.

BUSINESS ANALYST

PRISM BRANDS, CHICAGO, IL | APR 2013 - JUN 2016

- Lead design and deployment of Trackvia Cloud Database for inventory management and accounting purposes.
- Directed day to day warehouse & WeWork office operations while lowering costs and simplifying operations.
- Administrated various reporting projects for managing partner, including profitability and inventory reports.
- Managed ecommerce store & CPO marketing campaigns to maximize sales and minimize spend.
- · Pitched and secured big ecommerce contract with a Japanese manufacturer

ABOUT ME

Technical data scientist with approx. 5 years of experience solving complex business challenges and translating strategic thinking into actionable and analytical frameworks. Creative thinker, with domain knowledge in several industries including e-commerce, social media, automotive and esports. Founder of Coalescence.gg, a tech and everything-esports weekly newsletter, avid gamer and general believer that anything that can be measured, can be improved.

SKILLS

- Data analysis in code, spreadsheets & BI-tools.
- Visualizing data in Python, Excel, Tableau & more.
- Python

SQL

- BeautifulSoup NLP
- Excel • Seaborn
- Git Pandas
- Matplotlib
- HTML Keras
- Tensorflow

- Scala
- Tableau DOMO
- AWS
- Google Cloud Google Analytics